

BENEDICT VOLANTE

IT Staff

About Me

37-year-old Filipino, born December 15, 1986. Computer literate (Microsoft Word, Excel, PowerPoint, PHP, SQL, HTML and CSS). Committed to supporting two children for a better future.



(02)8255-2276/09099444713



volantebenedic@gmail.com



Block 5 Lot 11 Durian Street Doña Josefa Village, Las Piñas City

LANGUAGE

- English(basic)
- Filipino

EXPERTISE

- Creative
- Team player
- Hardworking
- Dependable
- Critical Thinking
- Quick Learner

EXPERIENCE

Specialized Project Limited Company (K.S.A.) August 2015 - September 2017

 Electrical Technician - wiring and installation of data cabinets. Installation of data and telephone cabinets, as well as CCTV systems.

·Yapi Merkezi Saudi Company (K.S.A.) January 2013 - January 2014

 Electrician - Installation of Lighting and Electrical devices.

TRAININGS

TRAINOVATE (February 11 - 15, 2019)

• CONSTRUCTION OCCUPATIONAL SAFETY & HEALTH (DOLE)

OJT CSK Corp (Aug. 14, 2023 - Oct. 26, 2023)

- · Language PHP, CSS, HTML, and JavaScript.
- Web Dev Team Attendance Management System)
- Social Media Role (Infographics using Canva and other relevant sites. Also Photo editor)

EDUCATION

Informatics College Northgate

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology 2020-2023

Adamson University

Bachelor of Science in Electrical Engineering 2004 - 2007

SKILLS SUMMARY

Driving Skills - Can drive 2 wheels and 4 wheels (non professiona